[{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664219371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":27544,"timeElapsed":179008},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664247255,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":27878,"timeElapsed":206892},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664259394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":12131,"timeElapsed":219032},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664269217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":9818,"timeElapsed":228855},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664275321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":6098,"timeElapsed":234959},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664279616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4290,"timeElapsed":239254},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664286460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6838,"timeElapsed":246098},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664294033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7568,"timeElapsed":253671},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"203","question":"What app on your phone do you use the most frequently? In what contexts do you use it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8846,"timeElapsed":262522},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664427406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":120896,"timeElapsed":387044},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664436767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":9357,"timeElapsed":396405},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664441740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4967,"timeElapsed":401377},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664444582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2837,"timeElapsed":404220},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664451017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":6428,"timeElapsed":410654},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664453097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2076,"timeElapsed":412735},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664455779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2675,"timeElapsed":415416},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664463069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7285,"timeElapsed":422707},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664470433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7355,"timeElapsed":430070},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664494430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":22840,"timeElapsed":454068},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664498798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4361,"timeElapsed":458436},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664505017,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":6214,"timeElapsed":464655},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664508503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3481,"timeElapsed":468141},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664511680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3170,"timeElapsed":471318},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664513543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1856,"timeElapsed":473181},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664515504,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1952,"timeElapsed":475142},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664520607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5097,"timeElapsed":480245},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664522939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2326,"timeElapsed":482577},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664537482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":13270,"timeElapsed":497120},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664540443,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2957,"timeElapsed":500081},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664544758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4311,"timeElapsed":504396},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664556483,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11720,"timeElapsed":516120},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664563337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":6851,"timeElapsed":522975},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664565412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2071,"timeElapsed":525050},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664566946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1529,"timeElapsed":526584},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664569115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2161,"timeElapsed":528753},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664576671,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7550,"timeElapsed":536309},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664583699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7022,"timeElapsed":543337},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664596305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":11538,"timeElapsed":555943},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664597808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1499,"timeElapsed":557445},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664599347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1532,"timeElapsed":558985},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664600776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1423,"timeElapsed":560414},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664602313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1529,"timeElapsed":561951},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664603785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":1466,"timeElapsed":563423},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664605359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":1568,"timeElapsed":564997},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664607482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2115,"timeElapsed":567119},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664609037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1551,"timeElapsed":568675},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664630539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":20394,"timeElapsed":590177},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664632135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1591,"timeElapsed":591773},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664633799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1658,"timeElapsed":593437},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664635422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1617,"timeElapsed":595060},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664636999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1569,"timeElapsed":596637},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664638404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1400,"timeElapsed":598042},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664639750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1337,"timeElapsed":599388},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664641241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1485,"timeElapsed":600878},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664643481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2235,"timeElapsed":603119},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664654025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":9492,"timeElapsed":613662},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664655348,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1317,"timeElapsed":614986},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664657489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2134,"timeElapsed":617127},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664658888,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1393,"timeElapsed":618526},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664661076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2183,"timeElapsed":620714},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664663883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2803,"timeElapsed":623520},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664665352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1464,"timeElapsed":624989},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664666812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1454,"timeElapsed":626450},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664668324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":1507,"timeElapsed":627962},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664683749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":14498,"timeElapsed":643387},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664685370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1616,"timeElapsed":645008},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664686766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1391,"timeElapsed":646404},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664688088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1317,"timeElapsed":647726},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664689545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1452,"timeElapsed":649183},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664691085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1538,"timeElapsed":650723},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664692536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1447,"timeElapsed":652174},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664697342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4798,"timeElapsed":656980},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664703768,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6422,"timeElapsed":663406},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664707081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"126","question":"Do you have any deceased relatives you wish you had been on better terms with before they passed? If you had an hour with them, what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3310,"timeElapsed":666719},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664713392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5022,"timeElapsed":673030},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664715797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":675434},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664717346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1543,"timeElapsed":676984},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664719095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1742,"timeElapsed":678733},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664720969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1869,"timeElapsed":680607},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664723094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":2120,"timeElapsed":682731},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664725027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1928,"timeElapsed":684665},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664728577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3545,"timeElapsed":688215},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664730978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2395,"timeElapsed":690615},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664741365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":9286,"timeElapsed":701003},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664742792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1423,"timeElapsed":702430},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664744338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1538,"timeElapsed":703975},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664745771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1429,"timeElapsed":705409},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664748224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2447,"timeElapsed":707862},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664750136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1907,"timeElapsed":709774},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664752550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2410,"timeElapsed":712188},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664755356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2802,"timeElapsed":714994},{"subjectID":"m66f37sc00","prolificID":"675c0780944016a1ad8c0ae7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215fbf8a434754bdc5fc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664757075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1715,"timeElapsed":716713}]